more left. And uh look, you can always
find a lot out with one to go. And uh
and no, we're not playing for the
playoffs, but but there's still things
we can find out. And uh you know, and
and I expect the guys that we have here
to to give it what they got one more
time. That's that's the expectation.
>> So Jazz, what what are some of the
things you can find out? how players
play, how they how they do on the road,
maybe a second time, how they play at
this position, uh how they handle the
pressure, how they handle with nothing
to play for. Um there's a little bit of
everything. Just find a lot out.
>> Are injured players, if any, have you
decided won't play, you know, this
weekend?
>> Uh well, the injury report is we're
pretty riddled right now. So I I don't
know, you know.
>> All year if those guys compete.
>> Yeah. No, I mean, we'll we'll find more
out here next day or two. I mean, if
they can play, we're we're playing, you
know, [snorts]
>> possibility of play playing some some
younger guys.
>> Any possibility of playing some some
younger? Are you going to treat this
just like a a normal week or maybe give
guys a few more reps that you maybe
wouldn't? How how do you want to
approach it that way? Yeah, I think if
if if guys can't go because of injury,
then then the next guy up will, you
know, we'll go young or old, it doesn't
or young or veteran, I should say, next
best guy available.
>> Brown came out at the end of the uh the
game last week. Did he come out of that
okay? Is there an update on him?
>> Yeah, I think long term he's going to be
okay, you know, which is good. That's
good news.
>> The knee again for him on that play.
>> That's part of it. Yep. I think maybe
rephrasing Dave's question, is
questionable different on injury report
when the game doesn't matter towards
playoffs, does it does it change the
definition of of that word at all?
>> Uh, yeah, I think so. I mean, I think if
it's if we're sitting there borderline
and the player it it could be it could
be hard or we think they're setting
themselves up for long-term
uh a long-term risk, then no, it's not
worth it. But if it's the, you know, the
stuff doesn't feel good and it's bumps
and bruises and it's um then no, it's
like the next game up for Aman Rogers.
Since you said longterm he'll be okay.
How about short term? Does that seems to
indicate that he wouldn't be avail?
Yeah, dayto-day. He wants to go, you
know, and uh he'll be dayto-day.
>> You have
>> he's improved, you know.
>> As you said, after the game you you you
have to look at everything and there's
this really big picture outlook of the
organization right now. How do you
do do you keep your focus 100% right now
on on what's ahead with the Bears or do
you start dipping into some of the big
picture stuff and getting a head start
on it now given the the pace I guess the
offseason starts moving right away?
>> Yeah. Well, I think um there's things
that you can't help but but think about,
you know, since that game um that that
go through my mind a little bit, but at
the same token, I know we have one more.
And I owe it to these guys uh to the
players and coaches to be locked in for
another game here cuz it's not fair to
go out there and say that we're going to
do everything we can prepare to win, but
we're not really doing that. That then
we shouldn't even go out there. Um, so I
I'm not there yet. You know, there's
things that have crossed my mind, but
I'm not I'm so far from all that.
[clears throat] Got to get ready for
this one.
>> How have the Bears changed since that
first meeting?
>> They're more polished. They're better
team. Um, you know, they're they've
really since that time they they lead
the league in in takeaways on defense.
You know, they're they're uh I mean,
they're getting them, man. They're it's
like we talk about it's contagious for
them. and those guys are getting them in
a good way. Got one uh the other night,
you know, once again that turned it for
to a touchdown. So, and [snorts] uh it's
much more sound. You know, DA's got his
system in and it's grown and developed.
Um and um you know, they're keeping
teams out of the end zone, staying uh
keeping the offense ahead. Um you know,
which is that's what you got to do on
defense, man. Get the takeaways. That's
big. Uh and then offensively, they're
more polished. You know, Ben's done a
good job. system is in and uh these
little things that were there game two,
game one, you know, they've began to go
away. It's it's uh um you know, they've
got a run game. They found a run game.
Play action pass. Caleb's playing really
well. O line's playing really well. Got
a run game. Swift's running well. 25 is
uh he's he's a downhill hard runner,
too. So, tight end's playing good, both
of them. Um really all three of them.
So, you know, they they've uh they're
they're playing at a high level. You
know, they're they're doing things well,
much more polished.
>> Gone through this as a a player and and
a coach. Dan, um just when you you've
got a ton of guys that are going to be
free agents, right? Like every year,
every team is different. How much do you
have to step back and appreciate, you
know, the guys that are are here that
have been here through it all? How much
do you emphasize that to the the roster?
like you know this is the last time this
this group's going to be together like
just you know appreciate this this last
moment to enjoy this team.
>> Well I think there is something to that
you know it because that is it is the
last time this group will be together
and uh you know you go through that
every year and um you know it certainly
we're not where we want to be with one
left but but at the same token um you
know this this group of guys has has
laid it on the line. and they've come to
work every day, bust their tail, and uh
and so really it's you got one more to
not let the guy next to you down. That
that's and that's how he's felt as a
player. It didn't matter how I felt or
what I thought, I couldn't let that guy
next to me down. That that's the
ultimate motivation
>> with uh I obviously been, you know,
tough three weeks here, but is there any
area in particular was position group,
side of the football, whatever, where
you'd really like to see a a strong
finish on Sunday? Well, yeah, every
group. I mean, um
I mean that's Yeah, there I mean, look,
there's a number of areas. Um
you know, I'd love to see um
I mean, there's there's a lot of areas,
you know, I'd probably start with the O
line just want to see, you know, and
just to just to tick more, you know,
just a little bit better. see if we can
polish some things up. Uh work together,
you know, work our combinations just a
little bit. That's, you know, but I can
say that for every position, too. I
really can. Um just like I can say that
for us as coaches. I mean, we we got to
collectively all get better.
>> Asked you about Tyreek last week and his
growth. Um Tate has played more than any
of your rookies. I'm just curious just
going back to to week one and maybe some
of the communication struggles to to
where he's at now. Um, how pleased have
you been with with his growth? How good
do you feel about him kind of going
forward with his career?
>> I'm sorry, you're talking about Yeah,
about Rattlage. Uh, there's been growth,
you know, and that's that's really what
you want out of your rookies. You want
to feel like that that there has been
growth taking place. Um,
and uh, you know, being between Graham
for most of the year and Soul has helped
um, you know, but there's a ton of
growth left and uh, you know, he's going
to have to take another step. He's going
to have to take another step next year.
You know, preferably this next game
coming up, take another baby step here,
but he he's, you know, he's going to
need to take another step, which he's
got that he's capable of.
>> What do you think his ultimate position
is?
>> Uh, that's a good question. You know, I
know that we were, you know, we felt
like he could be a center. Um, and
that's still that's not off the table.
Um, you know, we've watched him at
guard. He played right guard in college.
Um, you know, he's a good athlete. He's
a big man. he can move. Um, so we'll
we'll find out. I mean, we'll find out.
>> Depending on what Graham status is,
would you give him a look at center this
week? Could that be in the mix at all?
Or
>> I don't see that. Yeah, I don't see
that.
>> Thank you.
>> Thanks,
[music]
Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
Heat. Heat. N.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Oh yeah.
Heat. Heat. N.
[music]